Piece by piece
You're leaving me in pieces on display
for good while I'm fine and understood
As I rattle my cell
and recomputing molecules
in prison bars
Shot at my foot and not the stars
OH!
Ain't that a shame?
My illness, a game?
You've set yourself as queen and me as the pawn
A move to the right
and you're out of sight
well, isn't that a pain you're finally gone!
(oooh my god!)
(Yay!)
(music)
Recomputing, counting the hours
by their watching, waiting for years
while they're begging tearfully
What's the point?
Am I really crying, shedding,
letting somebody, anybody, use me for a utility?
Utilizing, realizing god made me for a shameful purpose
worthless, notice why
Oh, why am I still alive?
Could it be that life isn't worth the stife anyway?
Oh my, what a sight!
You've put up a fight!
You've set yourself upright to be quite the show!
A move to the left
You're all out of help, well, isn't it a pain you reap what you sow!
(oooh my god!)
(recomputing)
(piece by piece)
(ain't that a shame?)
(counting the hours by their watching)
(You're leaving me in pieces)
(My illness a game?)
(waiting for years)
(You've set yourself as queen and me as the pawn)
(on display, for good)
(while they're begging tearfully)
(while I'm fine and understood)
(What's the point? Am I really crying, shedding)
(letting somebody, anybody, use me for a utility)
(As I rattle my cell)
(A move to the right)
(and recomputing molecules)
(and you're out of help!)
(god made me for a shameful purpose)
(in prison bars)
(well, isn't that a pain you're finally gone!)
(worthless, notice why)
(Shot at my foot and not the stars!)
(oh why am I still alive? Could it be that life isn't worth-)
OH!